[..]
I wanna be your vacuum cleaner
Breathing in your dust
I wanna be your Ford Cortina
I will never rust
If you like your coffee hot
Let me be your coffee pot
You call the shots, babe
I just wanna be yours
Secrets I have held in my heart
Are harder to hide than I thought
Maybe I just wanna be yours
I wanna be yours
Let me be your leccy meter
And I'll never run out
Let me be the portable heater
That you'll get cold without
I wanna be your setting lotion (salto) (wanna be)
Hold your hair in deep devotion (salto) (How deep?)
At least as deep as the Pacific Ocean
Now I wanna be yours
Secrets I have held in my heart
Are harder to hide than I thought
Maybe I just wanna be yours
I Wanna be yours
Wanna be yours
I want to be yours
I want to be along